This is Trigun.
Oh, my God.
Do you really want out here?
It's 500 yards to town. Thanks
for the ride! It's okay.
You aren't gonna listen, are you?
Well, teach his own.
Serious sandstorms are forming, up to
4,000 yards around the Orleans area.
All transportation has been stopped,
with no immediate signs of resuming.
Well, I suppose we're stuck here.
I don't know.
Why don't we just think of it
as some kind of vacation, Meryl?
If this were a vacation, I know that I'd
spend it someplace a lot quieter than this.
I did it! Unbelievable.
Not again?
I did it, I did it!
It's an all-club straight!
It's wonderful, Miss Stephanie.
Hey, I really like this game!
I can't play like this. Huh?
But wait, where are you going?
Don't give up yet!
I was just starting to have some fun here!
Showing myself would
be more fun than this.
Hey there, would you two like to play?
Are you playing All Made?
Well, actually, we don't know any
other games, but thank you very much.
Come on, don't be that way, please.
I'll play Deal Me In.
Well, all right then.
Let's get this show on the
road before my luck changes.
One condition.
Huh?
High stakes gain.
The bet is for your life.
There are three things I
can't tolerate in this world.
People who put ice and alcohol,
the pattern on a silhouette scorpion, and
slime who don't appreciate tranquility.
A robbery in my jurisdiction?
Not on my watch, damn it.
Well, what's the situation here, Stan?
All right, Dick.
Will you inform the Earl what's going on?
Yes, sir.
Well, according to the
testimony from the witnesses,
the group consists of four
criminals and four hostages.
I had a chance to talk to the
folks that escaped and they told
me that one of the hostages is a
real pretty girl who loves cards.
Mr.
Bostock, what are these
lowlifes looking for? Well,
they want a hundred
thousand double dollars
and in consecutive bills
and a getaway wagon.
Did they go and commit this crime
knowing that she's my daughter?
I bet they did.
I don't think it's any big secret
that you're the wealthiest man in town
and only you could come up with a hundred
thousand double dollars that quick.
I'm not gonna let them get away.
If word of this gets around, hooligans
will come swarming from everywhere.
My daughter will become their
plaything and when they're finished,
they'll discard her in the desert.
I suppose you wouldn't know that
from personal experience, would you?
Grim Reaper, postdoc, shut up. Stan,
you're supposed to be the sheriff in this
town and it's your job
to help my daughter.
Damn it.
I don't care how many have to die.
You need to do what it takes
to get her back in one piece.
Don't order me around postdoc.
This is not the old days
What is he doing?
Who is that idiot?
I have no idea. Hey! Look out!
Get back here, dumbass!
There's a hostage situation!
In there!
You want to die?
He's dancing around too
much to even notice!
He can't hear a damn thing!
That brainless moron.
He's gonna upset the criminals.
Dang fool!
He's dodging the bullets. Dodging?
That freak doesn't even
realize he's being shot at.
Looks like he's going inside.
Stop it!
Get out of there!
Who are you supposed to be?
Are you suicidal?
Or too stupid to know better?
Help somebody, robbers!
Help somebody!
Stop it!
That guy's just an idiot.
Takes more than just an idiot
to be screaming that way.
Please, somebody help!
Well, I guess we got five hostages now.
The plan has not changed.
All this means is that there's one more
life on the line we've got to worry about.
How's it coming along?
We got through just
about two hours ago, sir.
We'll be ready by the deadline
the criminals gave us, no problem.
Hey, Bostock,
I think it'd be a good idea for you to
keep praying for your daughter's safety.
Oh, yeah, and by the way, while
you're at it, don't forget the money.
Can't you be a little
more gentle, brother?
I won't try anything else.
Honest, you can even take my gun, see?
Huh? What's this?
Here catch oh that's heavy custom made huh
you're packing some serious firepower for
such a scrawny guy hey if you don't mind
could you give it back
to me when you're done?
shut up you little maggot
well hello hello you know
what i've been going
through a lot of hell since
i met the two of you we
are the ones that are in
hell you idiot oh that
really hurt are you okay oh?
Whoa!
What? What is it?
Hey, stop it!
Get away from me!
You're a creep.
This is not the way a
lady should be treated.
I am appalled by her lack of manners.
We are ladies too, you know.
Oh yeah, guess I forgot.
This lady's a special case.
She serves as a warning.
What do you mean?
They must want my family's money.
That has to be it.
Why else would they rob
this two-bit saloon?
How could you ever forgive
me, Miss Stephanie?
I failed to protect you. Dressing!
I hope you weren't thinking of
demanding anything too extravagant.
However,
if it's pocket money you want, I'm sure
I can easily get that from my daddy.
Pocket money.
Damn you!
Kill her!
I'll kill you right now!
Knock it off, Jean!
Stephanie!
Stop!
I'll pull the trigger!
I swear!
I'll just cry!
Screw you, Daniel!
Calm down.
You've got to get a
hold of yourself, Gene.
You better keep your mouth shut, cause
next time it just might be me with the gun.
Can't we all just get along?
Peaceful-like?
Huh?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry! Somebody help me!
Gum?
You're kidding.
It couldn't be.
You're using them?
Yes,
they're a lovely bunch of
mercenaries who would do anything,
even kill their very own families
just to get a little bit of money.
They're actually quite
skillful and best of all,
they have no respect for each other.
They are the perfect men for the child.
And they'll take control of the situation.
Take my word, Willa.
I trust they won't
accidentally shoot my daughter?
Now that all depends on how
much money you offer them.
Think of it this way, unless
you make it worth their while,
they won't be able to tell
her apart from a sandroach.
Ain't that right?
Give them what they want.
But they'd better not lay
a finger on my daughter!
Okay, got yourself a tea.
Now let's get this little
party underway, shall we?
Get it through your head, moron!
Ah, right.
Damn!
Time is running out, you little weasels.
You all had better hope the
wagon and money gets here.
And I don't want to hear about any more
delays or I'm gonna have to get angry
That's enough of that denim.
We still got work to do
Excuse me if you receive
the money you're asking for
will you promise to release
miss Stephanie unharmed?
It's all up to her father for her sake.
I hope he doesn't do anything stupid
keep it down The satellites on
Vash the Stampede. What?
Yeah, that's what I heard.
The Humanoid Typhoon is in this city.
Hey, if Big Man Bostock or the Sheriff
hires Vash the Stampede, the party's over.
We'll all be dead before sunrise.
Don't go losing your head.
Keep it together now, guys.
It's almost time. Hey, look!
Something's coming this way! Shut up!
I told you to stay still!
Alright.
It's here, man. It's the wagon.
Stay down.
All right.
Here's your wagon and $100,000
double dollars in consecutive bills.
We have met your demands.
Release your hostages immediately!
Not quite yet.
First we check the wagon and the money.
And you listen up!
Try anything, and the hostages
are dead meat! Got that?
I'll go.
You be careful.
Do you think your father will hand
over the money without trying anything?
My daddy will do anything to
protect me, no matter what it takes.
Stan's another matter.
It's a trap!
Marvin!
That bastard!
Get back here, Gene!
Oh no, Gene!
You okay?
I think so.
Is this how they work in this town?
This is really stupid.
Yeah, I'd say it's a bit overboard.
Like I was gonna say, he's
not exactly a normal sheriff.
You!
Huh?
Oh, never mind.
You probably could have slipped
out of the ropes at any time.
But who in the head?
Hey, Mr. Robberman!
Why don't you show us your pretty face?
Yeah, we'd be happy to make it a lot
prettier with some hotline surgery!
What do we do now?
I have no idea.
So, can we kill him, hmm?
You can kill anyone but the girl! Cool.
Stop, I beg you!
Please, don't shoot!
You know what, friend?
Anyone ever tell you
that you lack compassion?
What's the matter?
Just shoot the guy!
Now, tough guy, so I guess you
think you have a hostage now!
Just shoot him!
Then we'll all make
more money on this deal!
Rem...
This guy really is a stupid ass!
Everybody, what in the
hell were you thinking?
What made you decide you
weren't going to shoot him?
I'm really glad that you didn't shoot him.
Me too.
Because I don't like pain very much.
Ah, never mind.
Are you okay now? Do you?
Understand the sheriff never had any
intention of giving you any money.
I'll Ask daddy to let you go free if you
will promise to just stop all of this.
That's not something I can do.
What I have reasons for
what I've done here.
Do You know anything about the huge
graveyard on the northeast outskirts of?
the town.
Our parents are buried beneath that hellish
wasteland, where now even the corpse
weeds won't grow.
I remember them working like animals
in the fields, covered in dirt.
Finally, after ten years, they managed
to make this sandy soil usable.
It was an amazing
Accomplishment then about 15 years ago
your father showed up and stole the land.
Those good people sweated blood to plow
he earned the name Grim Reaper Bostock.
When he slaughtered them
all at this point line would
accomplish nothing we We
don't care about the money.
Whatever happens, I will not run away.
However, I will take revenge
for what happened 15 years ago.
Mark my words.
It's impossible to forget
something like that.
Huh? What's happening?
What the hell?
Hey, don't you worry.
We'll get you some help, pal.
Am I gonna die?
No, it's all right.
You're gonna be okay.
The bullet passed right through.
Attention!
I will now discuss the demands
on behalf of these men.
You're going?
He has my oldest daughter.
I have no other choice.
But hear this, Stan.
When all of this is over, I will
hold you personally responsible.
He was feared fifteen years
ago as Grim Reaper Bostock.
Amazing how the love of a daughter in
the passage of time can change a man.
You have what you want now.
It's time to release the girl, Ingwe.
Please forgive me for
what I'm about to do.
It's not an easy thing to escape
from a past you can't bury.
You can't look away anymore.
It's time you face the
truth about your father.
You can no longer remain ignorant
of the hopes of the people
because of the terrible lie
your entire life was built upon.
I am aware of that.
But, even if it is true that he was
responsible for all those horrible things,
he is still my daddy.
No matter how disobedient
or selfish I was growing up,
he was always a warm, dedicated
and loving father to me.
Father!
Father, I'm coming!
Daddy, hold on! Daddy! Daddy!
Please, Daddy, no!
I'm I'm all right, honey.
It's only my shoulder.
What are you crying about?
Listen, I don't want you
thanking me for anything.
I just simply got distracted
and it threw my aim off.
That's all
Can't believe he's really crying
See you later.
I'm turning myself in.
Whoa there.
It's too soon for the epilogue.
It's all over, Stan.
I'm gonna give myself up. Not yet.
I still need you to resist me. What?
I never dreamed that I would be
presented with such an opportunity.
I can see the headlines now.
Besieged criminal kills Mr. Bostock.
Sheriff forced to shoot culprit
down as he attempts to resist.
It makes for a pretty article.
A real showpiece for my scrapbook.
No, Stan.
The sheriff is a position of honor.
How could you do this?
Fifteen years ago, this man
stole every right to this town.
I should have been just as powerful.
Yet I was stuck as the lowly sheriff.
I think I'm way past due to receive
a little glory around these parts.
You were in on it.
You're a fiend.
You're a scoundrel.
Throw down your weapons right now.
You unarmed stray dogs.
How grand to be superior.
I have one question.
Tell me, how does it feel to kill
unarmed innocent people like that?
And I have a question for you.
Do you feel anything when
you burn your garbage?
Nifty answer. Sorry I asked.
What? What the?
That was awesome!
How did you figure out that I was armed?
I don't remember telling you about it.
Remember?
You helped me in the saloon.
I can recognize the smell of
gunpowder and grease instantly.
Well, now...
You bastards! I'll...
Well, what do you think, Sheriff?
How does it feel to be at the
mercy of a stray dog, huh?
You can relax, Sheriff.
I'm not going to kill you.
However, you...
No longer have the right to be Sheriff.
Wanna know something interesting, Sheriff?
Repeat carefully after me Okay,
Thank you.
Oh,
I'll see you, I'll see you,
I'll see you,
I'll
see
you.
What is lost will never return.
Important things, irreplaceable things.
But what is needed to keep those things is
in the firm will, packed into one bullet.
Man knows, he knows that nothing
will begin unless he speaks.
And that nothing will
change unless he moves.